<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WattLab</title>
    <link>http://www.WattLab.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WattLab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 17:40:55 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.WattLab.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>写在前面</title>
      <link>http://www.WattLab.net/%E5%86%99%E5%9C%A8%E5%89%8D%E9%9D%A2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 17:40:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.WattLab.net/%E5%86%99%E5%9C%A8%E5%89%8D%E9%9D%A2/</guid>
      <description>去年毕业，到现在已经一年有余了。 毕业的时候不想去电网，觉着电网混吃等死，没有意义。像我这样的穷小子，本来就什么都没有，索性就任性的闯一闯，反正结果也不会差到哪里去-自己养活自己肯定还是没问题的。 于是来到了台达。 前两个月过的还算顺畅，基本没有安排任务，就是把电路图拿出来看了一遍。说是看了一遍，起始很多地方都没有细算，大体的缕一缕结构就放到那了。 后来忙了一点点，但关键性的活都不是我做，我就负责给机器上电，看一下工作或者故障情况，如果故障了，把机器拆开，放平，关键信号用探头勾出来，让老工程师分析，跟着学习。 然后是解Thermal，把变压器，电感，半导体的温度用热耦线点出来，放在Chamber里跑，看最高能到多少度，能不能满足derating。变压器core热或者wire热，我都不知道如何处理，只能拿着数据去找老大，让他给建议。按他的建议，再点热耦线，再测，反反复复测了很久。 进步的很缓慢，我甚至觉着自己什么都没干，公司就每个月给我发了工资。工作的积极性呢，说高不高，总觉着自己没什么实力，做什么事情都不敢自己拿决定，要去咨询老工程师，得到他们的首肯，才敢做。老工程师们就开始变的不耐烦：同事帮你是情谊，不帮你也正常。 天天做这些事儿，总觉着不踏实，人是飘着的，说是电源工程师，既不熟悉拓扑，也不熟悉器件，管子不会选，变压器电感不会设计，控制电路也是一踏糊涂。 而且我发现，很多人对这些都是一知半解。。 但这并不妨碍他们做电源，一个部门里有上两三个头脑清醒，思维清晰的人，就可以撑着往前运转了。
如果决定都让别人做，你的作用是什么呢，不动脑子，机械的执行？执行力固然重要，但背后的思维更重要，这也是为什么会有这个网站的原因。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://www.WattLab.net/%E6%A8%A1%E7%89%88/creating-a-new-theme1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.WattLab.net/%E6%A8%A1%E7%89%88/creating-a-new-theme1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>停停停停停停</title>
      <link>http://www.WattLab.net/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.WattLab.net/test/</guid>
      <description> 摘要 功率校正电路对离线电源波形进行整形，以使从电源吸取的有功功率最大化。 为了符合规范的要求，在全球销售产品，电源必须采用PFC  定义 对于电压和电流都是正弦波，功率因数为电压电流相位角度余弦。 对于非正弦电路，谈论 相位角 是没有意义的。而离线电源的输入电压是电网电压，是正弦波。输入电流的非正弦，可以分析其谐波含量。  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://www.WattLab.net/%E6%A8%A1%E7%89%88/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.WattLab.net/%E6%A8%A1%E7%89%88/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>http://www.WattLab.net/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 12:49:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.WattLab.net/links/</guid>
      <description>Ritchie and his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.WattLab.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 12:50:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.WattLab.net/about/</guid>
      <description>你好，我是一名电源工程师。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://www.WattLab.net/%E6%A8%A1%E7%89%88/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.WattLab.net/%E6%A8%A1%E7%89%88/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://www.WattLab.net/%E6%A8%A1%E7%89%88/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.WattLab.net/%E6%A8%A1%E7%89%88/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>